{"data":[{"question":"Which of the students in your class made ___ mistakes?","a":"fewer","b":"a few","c":"the least","d":"the fewest","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Superlative comparison: The + (Most) Superlative Adjectives (+ noun) \n+ Little- less- least ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"It is _________ that we will win the match.","a":"sure","b":"surely","c":"certain","d":"certainly","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We often say \"it is certainly true\/possible \"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Ron is ___ interested in English. He often studies it until ___ into the night.","a":"deeply, deep","b":"deep, deep","c":"deeply, deeply","d":"deep, deeply","answer":"1","explain":"\n- An adverb modifying an adjective will often answer \"how\" or \"to what extent\" for adjectives ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Iron is ___ steel.","a":"differ from","b":"different with","c":"difference than","d":"different from","answer":"4","explain":".\n- Be different from","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Have you ever gone on a trip? \"Oh, about, ___.\"","a":"dozens of time","b":"a dozen of time","c":"a dozen times","d":"dozen of times","answer":"3","explain":". \n- A doze + noun(s): a lot of \n- Dozens of sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"That is one of the best experiences I have _________ had.","a":"never","b":"once","c":"ever","d":"before","answer":"3","explain":".\n- Ever: \t a word meaning at any time; used mostly in questions, negatives, comparisons, or sentences with 'if","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Have you finished your sewing yet? \"No, I'll finish in _________ thirty minutes.\"","a":"other","b":"another","c":"less","d":"more","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Another: one more person or thing of the same type","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Your brother will go with you _________ the next 2 stops.","a":"as far as","b":"as long as","c":"so far as","d":"so long as","answer":"1","explain":"\n- As far as: To the degree or extent that \n- As long as: On the condition that ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The hurricane kept my family ___ all through the night.","a":"awoke","b":"awake","c":"awoken","d":"awaked","answer":"2","explain":"\n - Awake(adj): not sleeping","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Our school is five minutes ___.","a":"far from the bus stop","b":"from the bus stop away","c":"away from the bus stop","d":"far away from the bus stop","answer":"3","explain":"-\u00a0Away from: used for talking about the direction of a road, path","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}